There‘s no doubt that in today’s digital world, computer games are extremely sophisticated and capable of creating virtual reality experiences that were unimaginable only a few years ago.
毫无疑问，在当今的数字世界中，电脑游戏极其复杂精妙，能够创造出几年前还难以想象的虚拟现实体验。
So I am interested to see that the simplistic games that I grew up with, are making a revival.
所以，我很有兴趣看到我小时候玩的那些简单的游戏正在复兴。
But why?
但这是为什么呢？
In the 1970s, the original place to play a computer game was at an arcade.
在20世纪70年代，玩电脑游戏的最初场所是游戏厅。
Here, you and your mates could try out the new big names in games such as Space Invaders and Pacman.
在那里，你和你的伙伴们可以试玩一些新的知名游戏，比如《太空侵略者》和《吃豆人》。
It was the only affordable way to play them and because of the technology involved, the gaming machines were too big to fit in to your house.
这是玩这些游戏唯一能负担得起的方式，而且由于当时所涉及的技术原因，游戏机太大了，无法放在家里。
But in the 1980s and 90s, gaming arrived in our homes and people like me were addicted.
但在20世纪80年代和90年代，游戏进入了我们的家庭，像我这样的人都上瘾了。
The sound of beeping became a familiar sound emanating from bedrooms across the land!
哗哗声成了全国各地卧室里传出的熟悉声音！
Names such as Tetris, Sonic and Street Fighter became popular language in the playground — and now they are being talked about — and played — again.
像《俄罗斯方块》、《索尼克》和《街头霸王》这样的游戏名称在操场上成了流行词汇—而现在它们又被人们谈论和玩起来了。
One of the reasons is the low cost.
其中一个原因是成本低。
The BBC spoke to gamer, Gemma Wood, who says that: “Newer consoles and their games are incredibly expensive.
英国广播公司采访了游戏玩家杰玛·伍德，她说：“更新的游戏主机及其游戏贵得令人难以置信。
I understand that a lot of hard work has gone into the design etc, but how can anyone justify £50 to £60 for a game that you might not even enjoy?”
我理解在设计等方面投入了大量的努力，但对于一个你可能根本不喜欢的游戏，怎么能有人认为花50到60英镑是合理的呢？”
Simplicity might be another reason.
简单可能是另一个原因。
The graphics on old games may not compare with the detail and definition of modern games but they are fun and easy to use by children and adults alike.
老游戏的图像可能比不上现代游戏的细节和清晰度，但它们很有趣，而且孩子和大人都很容易上手。
And of course, nostalgia plays its part.
当然，怀旧也起了作用。
Some people want to relive their childhood, and for others it‘s a chance to show their own children the computer games they used to play.
有些人想重温他们的童年，而对另一些人来说，这是一个向他们的孩子展示自己小时候玩的电脑游戏的机会。
Technology journalist, KG Orphanides, says we should have admiration for this old technology.
科技记者KG·奥尔法尼德斯说，我们应该对这种老技术怀有钦佩之情。
He says “it’s important to recognise how well-designed many of those classic games are... the developers had so little space to work with — your average Sega Mega Drive or SNES cartridge had a maximum capacity of just 4MB — and limited graphics and sound capabilities.”
他说：“认识到许多经典游戏的设计是多么出色是很重要的......开发者可用的空间非常小——普通的世嘉超级驱动游戏机或超级任天堂游戏卡带的最大容量只有4MB——而且图像和声音功能也有限。”
This compares to an average capacity of 40G in today‘s games.
这与如今游戏平均40G的容量形成了鲜明对比。
This craze for using retro hardware and grabbing an old joystick is certainly catching on.
使用复古硬件和拿起旧操纵杆的这股热潮肯定正在流行起来。
And to persuade those of us who are not sure about downgrading the gaming experience, manufacturers such as Nintendo, are bringing back some of their older consoles in new style casing.
为了说服我们中那些对降低游戏体验持怀疑态度的人，像任天堂这样的制造商正在用新样式的外壳重新推出一些他们的旧款游戏机。
So it seems like it‘s not ’game over‘ for old-school technology!
所以，看起来老式技术还没有“游戏结束”！